Translated by Releska
I'll give you a chance to become a boy
Of course, you'll always be here
I'll be with you, I'll be with you
There's a picture of you, right?
You and you and you
If you love me,
I'll be able to be with you
I don't want to be with you
Hello?
Let's go!
Everyone, let's eat
Hey, Nakira-kun, eat a lot
That's a head
Don't make a bad impression
Oh, stop it!
If you go to the bag, I'll put it in the bag
I'll put it in the bag
Where did it go?
Huh?
It's strange, it was so cute that I had a stomachache
Oh, it's not a bag
I'll put it in the bag tomorrow
Huh? Are you still angry?
Let's go
Oh, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Huh?
See you again
Hey
It's so cute
It's okay, it's okay
It's so cute that I had a stomachache
Huh?
Wait, wait!
Where did it go?
A tren?
It's good to eat
Let's relax
Huh?
Don't you eat?
Yeah
I'm going to eat! I'm going to eat right now!
If you're hungry, you're not going to eat at all!
I'm sorry, I don't have much to say.
I'm going to eat at the other side too!
Are you sure you're hungry?
What did you say from Yo-chan?
Well, that's not good.
I'm looking forward to seeing you.
You're sweet, aren't you?
Well, that's right. Yo-chan's friendship is like that.
I'm going to sleep.
You're not going to die, right?
You're not going to die?
Are you going to die?
I'm not going to die!
Ah!
Ah! I wonder if I can get in the way!
I'm hungry!
Hey!
What are you doing here?
My brother, my mother!
Oh!
What?
I just came here to eat.
I'm not going to eat anything.
You're stupid.
Hey! Stop it!
You can't do anything!
You're stupid, right?
Hey! Stop it!
I'm going to have to get out of here.
Hey!
You're not going to do anything.
I'm not going to eat anything.
Hey!
You're getting out of the face.
I'll tell you.
It's okay to talk about the company.
You're going to get out of the face.
What are you two doing?
I don't know what I'm trying to do.
I'm going to...
Well, you said you were going to go to the station, right?
Yes.
Hey, you!
Wait a minute!
I'll do it.
I don't want to go to the station!
You said you wanted to go to the station, right?
That's right!
I'm looking forward to seeing you in the next episode!
Really?
What do you mean by that?
Hey, you!
Anyway, I want to go to the station.
Yes, sir.
Let's go!
Hey, you!
Stop it!
What's wrong, you!
You look cute!
Did you buy anything?
Not really!
You're lying!
Huh?
I got it!
I took a bad look at the test again!
It's wrong.
Show it to me!
No!
It's wrong!
It's not right!
You want to go to the station?
No!
It's wrong!
Show it to me!
No!
I want to go to the station!
Show it to me!
No!
It's not right!
I want to go to the station!
Sorry!
Hey, Lanca!
Do you want to go to the station?
Don't you want to go to the station?
No, I don't!
Hey, that's Kyoryu.
Is it the opposite?
Then, you'll go to the station right now?
Oh, that's not right.
I'm not right.
I don't want to go.
I don't want to go to the station!
It's 4 years.
I don't even know what you're saying.
No!
Don't do that!
You're really going to go to the station!
What?
A station?
That's right!
If you keep doing that,
you'll become a pretty good person!
I'm going to go to the station!
What do you think?
It's not a bad thing.
I'm not going to go to the station.
Okay.
Is that something you're looking for?
I'm not.
You're here, Ranka.
I'm going to go to the station!
It's not a bad thing.
I'm not going to go to the station.
It's a good thing.
You're going to go to the station!
Stop!
I'm going to go to the station!
It's a good thing.
I don't want to go to the station where my mom would be.
I'm going to go to the station!
You're going to go to the station!
I'm not going to go to the station!
I'm going to go to the station today!
Baka, do you think I can get back to this?
Tuku, take no more!
I'm going to take no more!
What the hell?!
I'm going to lose!
Ah, it's me!
Nice catch!
It's me, Tuku!
You two should be together!
I'll take this!
No!
Muka Muka! Muka Muka!
Ah! The cat fell!
This is the✨
Google Play
It's that œκε
Yes!
It's that
Easy!
That's pretty good!
That's the end
Pet dalla ma, suLa ma ma
There, there
Let's go!
Go!
It's hot!
Kyon-chan!
Huh?
R-Rion?
Ah!
The bird's tail!
I want to talk to you!
No, I didn't use that much.
It's my fault!
Did you really run away?
Hmm, I lost.
I don't think I can get a car.
A car?
Yeah, the animal's tail is very important.
Especially, a big guy like Muka Muka will be able to eat and eat.
Huh?
Please take care of the car in the morning.
Please take care of Ui-ba.
Huh? Me too?
It's Muka Muka, so I have to take care of Ui-ba.
Ui-ba!
I've been looking around for 3 minutes.
No, Ui-ba!
I'll take care of the car.
Huh?
I'll take care of the car too.
Oh, I see.
Let's go.
Yeah!
It's good.
If you're with Hazuki-chan, you'll be happy.
Is Yoh-chan happy?
Yeah, yeah.
I think I'm happy.
Huh? Shibelia-san?
Hazuki-chan is also happy to take care of Ui-ba.
Huh? Really?
If we were with Ui-ba,
I wouldn't be able to run away even if I had to ride on the ride.
Huh?
Itaizental clinic.
It's here.
There's a center.
It's a pretty good company.
What are you doing?
It's not like a company.
It's a good company.
It's a nice company.
It's not like a company.
I see!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Ui-ba!
Life is a difficult and painful thing.
Huh?
Do this!
I got it, isn't it?
Shibelia Hazuki-san, please enter!
Yes!
Uiba, then I'll leave!
Ah, five points!
What do you think, Muka Muka-chan?
You're right. Everyone is bad.
I'm not a Seibaka, but you're right!
Well, I thought it was a little bad, so I gave it to you.
You're right. When you're doing the cooking, you're right.
It's good, isn't it? You can eat it every time you want.
I'm sure you're right, but...
I'm sure you're right.
What's going on?
I love you. Are you all right?
Well, since I feel like it, I'll go home early, but I'm glad you're here.
Shikata-ni-san!
What's going on?
Yes, please take care of it. I'm begging you.
But it's not easy for me.
You're right, Mr. Haishu. You're human, so you're the same as today.
I told you that.
Muka Muka, please.
Hey!
You're right, Muka Muka.
Muka Muka, are you doing well?
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka, please open your mouth.
Don't you think it's a day?
No, it's not a day.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Let's start from you.
Open your mouth.
Muka Muka, please open your mouth.
Muka Muka, what are you doing?
Help me!
I'm sorry, Muka Muka!
What are you doing, Muka?
Ah, Muka Muka!
I'm sorry, Muka Muka.
I'm sorry, Muka.
It's my fault.
What are you doing?
You're the first one to die!
What?!
Huh?!
Let's go.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I feel a little bit longer.
Huh?
If this food was not eaten by this, what should we do?
It's not good.
Huh?
What's wrong?
There's a little bird in the mouth.
Oh, it's true.
I see. There's a bird in the mouth.
That's good.
I don't think it's your fault.
That's really good.
Itadakimasu!
Huh?!
It's five o'clock.
Huh?
I'm going to start.
I'm getting better than this?
I'm getting better than this.
Huh?
I'm worried.
Even if I die, my arm will be hurt.
I get it.
It's already late.
How can I start?
I can't stop it.
I'm afraid.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I'm coming.
If it are to be seen, who is it, what is it anyway?
Hurry up to the room.
But I still getLAUGH.
We're hard so
Come on, Come on, Come on, Come on, Come on
Let's run fast, Come on, Come on, Come on, Come on,
Let's run, Come on, Come on, All the stars in the sky
It's fun really
Hurry up and run
It's only a few pages from another place.
Hey, it won't be a research show!
There are some points I want to ask about.
It must have been part of a show that can be an online tour or a great book,
but I'll explain it later.
Next up,
I'm looking forward to seeing you again at the time machine!